Luc Tan Do

Business Analyst/Scrum Master

I'm a Business Analyst/Scrum Master with over 3 years of experience in software development and digital transformation, working with leading companies in industry. I have a strong passion for learning new things to contribute significant impact solutions that streamline processes and improve user experiences. Experienced domains: Data Warehouse, HRMS, Finance, Supply Chain

dotanluc1301@gmail.com



0838327414





lucdo-portfolio.vercel.app/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Analyst DHL

03/2024 - Present

Responsibilities

- Build and maintain effective relationships with clients and stakeholders.
- Facilitate conversations with stakeholders to identify needs and create requirements.
- Ensure client satisfaction and gather feedback for continuous improvement.
- Monitor and measure the feature performance
- Support UAT with test cases and data

Business Analyst/Scrum Master bravoSUITE - Orient Software

06/2022 - 10/2023

Achievements/Tasks

- Collect and research the business needs by the demand of the product orientation and feedback.
- Inspect and conduct the gap analysis against the competitors in the market.
- Design wireframe, compose the models (by using UML) and document for requirement communication.
- Work closely with the development team to ensure requirements alignment and successful implementation.
- Present the demo with the relevant stakeholders and provide aid in training after release.
- Measure the release performance metrics and act accordingly with the result.
- Take Scrum delegation role in hosting events, facilitating communication, and crafting the Product roadmap with the technical base.

Software Engineer

CICAT - BOSCH

03/2019 - 05/2022

Responsibilities

- Implement new features and fix the existing defects.
- Take part in analysing requirements and eliciting the needs of stakeholders through open points.
- Provide remote technical support to customers via e-mail and Q&A meeting sessions.
- Manage and create release details on business documents.

EDUCATION

Information Technology | Software **Engineer**

HUFLIT (2016-2020)

SKILLS



CERTIFICATES

Scaled Professional Scrum (09/2024)

https://www.scrum.org/user/1370286/

C# (Basic) (09/2024)

https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/a5f8063755cb

Problem Solving (Basic) (09/2024)

https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/bf2bb1daa7a3

SQL (Intermediate) (09/2024)

https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/074e1150240a

SQL (Basic) (09/2024)

https://www.hackerrank.com/certificates/e273cca5658c

Professional Scrum Product Owner II (05/2024)

https://www.scrum.org/user/1370286/

EF SET English Certificate (04/2024)

https://cert.efset.org/mPQjYr

Professional Scrum Master II (03/2024)

https://www.scrum.org/user/1370286/

Professional Scrum Product Owner I (01/2024)

https://www.scrum.org/user/1370286/

Professional Scrum Master I (01/2024)

https://www.scrum.org/user/1370286/

LANGUAGES

Fnalish

Professional Working Proficiency

TOOLS

